

Aditya Prakash

Integration Developer

Highly dependable, self-driven, and motivated with a track record of delivering multiple successful Go-Live of IIB applications efficiently. Look forward to excelling through hard work, research, skills, and perseverace and work in a challenging environment that provides more opportunities to explore new things.

adityaprakash5642@gmail.com

Mumbai, India

github.com/adip-45

+91 8097881369

in linkedin.com/in/adityasrprakash

instagram.com/adislenses

WORK EXPERIENCE

Associate Consultant Capgemini

10/2019 - Present

Navi Mumbai, India

Responsibilities/Tasks

- Worked on designing and implementing IIB solutions to support application enhancement and change requests.
- Worked on data and record analysis.
- Managed coordination with Clients and all relevant stakeholders to plan and execute a successful migration of the server along with IIB and MQ version upgrade in all the environments.
- Designed UI/UX and developed the mobile application using React Native from scratch, developed the service layer using MuleSoft and DB designing for an innovative idea that will help the community in the health-care domain.
- Executed cloud migration from MuleSoft to AWS Lambda in order to optimize the latency.

Senior AnalystCapgemini

08/2018 - 09/2019

Navi Mumbai, India

Responsibilities/Tasks

- Developed Interfaces from high-level design documents.
- Managed all deployment activities and promoted applications to higher environments.
- Managed coordination with Clients and all relevant stakeholders to plan and execute a successful Go-live of the application.
- Worked as a Level 3 Support.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering (Electronics)Sardar Patel Institute of Technology

08/2014 - 05/2018

Mumbai. India

Courses

- Investment Tracking
 System
- Gestures to Speech Conversion
- Smart Helmet

SKILLS



ACHIEVEMENTS

Prime Minister's Scholarship under National Defence Fund for pursuing higher studies (08/2014 - 05/2018)

CERTIFICATES

MuleSoft Certified Developer - Level 1 (Mule 4) (07/2020 - 08/2022)

Agile Software Development (07/2020)

IBM Integration Bus V10 Application Development II (04/2019)

IBM Integration Bus V10 Application Development I (04/2019)

LANGUAGES

Engish Full Professional Proficiency Hindi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Marathi

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Sports Photography Trekking